[{"answer": "I am? I mean why", "docId": "shampoo.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I'm not. Maybe I am", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I don't want to talk about it..", "docId": "shampoo.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I don't care", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " A wash and set", "docId": "shampoo.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "No", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "shampoo.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Go where", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "You're late, we're all backed up and you're supposed to go to my friend", "docId": "shampoo.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Yes, my friend", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "shampoo.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I already said hello", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "About what", "docId": "shampoo.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Going where", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I called to tell you I was sending one over but the line was busy, you're always on the phone", "docId": "shampoo.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Who were you talking to", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I am", "docId": "shampoo.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Who do you think I was talking to", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Well, it's my friend", "docId": "shampoo.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Well they are. But we have problems. You say things are great with my friend. Is he going to marry you", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "What did you do", "docId": "shampoo.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " No, it sounds very sexy did you just stay by the sink all that time", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Maybe he's too flighty and irresponsible. That's why I asked if he was a fairy", "docId": "shampoo.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": " You suggested it, don't you think it's a good idea", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Yeah, baby. Things are great. Listen, there's my friend, whatta you want", "docId": "shampoo.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Chicken salad, my friend", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I just have to do one little thing", "docId": "shampoo.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I won't screw you up", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": " What", "docId": "shampoo.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Did I what", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "It'll ruin everything", "docId": "shampoo.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Don't, don't, don't..", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "... yeah", "docId": "shampoo.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": " Gee, this is great", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Then what do you think", "docId": "shampoo.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "I am not like my mother", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "That you're just like your mother", "docId": "shampoo.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "You are", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "I am not like my mother", "docId": "shampoo.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "I am not", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "You are", "docId": "shampoo.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "You are", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Is he an enemy", "docId": "shampoo.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "sort of a boyfriend", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": " Of course not... he's sort of a boyfriend", "docId": "shampoo.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Sort of", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": " oh yeah... what do you know about this guy", "docId": "shampoo.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": " this guy with my friend", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "She what", "docId": "shampoo.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "And who's my friend", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "Oh, my friend, there you are, you know my friend and uh uh INFO", "docId": "shampoo.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "Yes, my friend, my wi my friend", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Well, commercials. I read for a soap the other day", "docId": "shampoo.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "A daytime soap opera", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "And", "docId": "shampoo.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "What was it, somebody's daughter", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "No, I blew it, I blew it with my friend", "docId": "shampoo.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "You don't think so? I do", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "No bomb", "docId": "shampoo.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": " It's good if there's no bomb. If there is a bomb and we can't find it, that's not good", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": " What did you say your name was, sweetheart", "docId": "shampoo.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": " my friend", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "Two weeks from tomorrow", "docId": "shampoo.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "You're going", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "Stop it", "docId": "shampoo.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "Yes, yes, I did", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "Did you", "docId": "shampoo.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "What did you say", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "What, do you think I planned it", "docId": "shampoo.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "Didn't they tell you", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": "Why, why do you think that is", "docId": "shampoo.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": "Well, I don't know", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "Me", "docId": "shampoo.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": " I was gonna give you the money. Probably I was. Shit, I don't know, I don't know anything anymore", "qsentId": 74}, {"answer": "I don't either, my friend, I swear to you I don't", "docId": "shampoo.txt", "asentId": 77, "question": "What about her", "qsentId": 76}]